<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cathy Shih</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cathy Shih</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>80s Hairstyle In Unity</title>
      <link>/80s-hair-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/80s-hair-model/</guid>
      <description>80s Hairstyle In Unity URP I crafted a 80s hairstyle using Blender, adopting a common hair creation workflow often associated with ZBrush. The process involved sculpting the hair shape and placing hair card curves for with layers – from the base layer to breakups to transitional layer.
Hair cards creation was done entirely within Blender, utilizing its hair tools, geometry nodes, and shader nodes. The final render was done with a custom anisotropic highlight hair shader created with Unity&amp;rsquo;s Shader Graph in the Universal Render Pipeline (URP).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>404</title>
      <link>/404.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/404.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a 3D Artist and Shader Developer from Taiwan. I love making things visually appealing since I was a child. After receiving my B.A. in Creative Design from National Yunlin University of Science and Technology, I began my career in 2013 at a watch manufacturing company in Taiwan, where I design watch faces and packaging. My journey led me to explore marketing, where I was passionate about desiging various materials such as brand identities, websites, brochures and videos with the goal of positively expressing the business&#39;s identity and appealing to potential partners and customers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
