<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cathy Shih</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cathy Shih</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>80s Hairstyle In Unity</title>
      <link>/80s-hair-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/80s-hair-model/</guid>
      <description>80s Hairstyle In Unity URP I crafted a 80s hairstyle using Blender, adopting a common hair creation workflow often associated with ZBrush. The process involved sculpting the hair shape and placing hair card curves for with layers – from the base layer to breakups to transitional layer.
Hair cards creation was done entirely within Blender, utilizing its hair tools, geometry nodes, and shader nodes. The final render was done with a custom anisotropic highlight hair shader created with Unity&amp;rsquo;s Shader Graph in the Universal Render Pipeline (URP).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>404</title>
      <link>/404.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/404.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I started my art and design journey in 2013 at a watch manufacturing company in Taiwan, where I worked as a Associate Watch Designer. Following this role, I utilized my design skills in various sales and marketing initiatives, including websites development, brand identities creation, and the designs of presentations and marketing materials. Although I found fulfillment in the creativity and challenges of business-oriented work, I felt like exploring challenges that allow me to express my art and design skills through the creation of games and narratives.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
